<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>20 and back</title>
    <link>https://20andback.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 20 and back</description>
    <image>
      <title>20 and back</title>
      <url>https://20andback.co/images/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://20andback.co/images/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://20andback.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jason Rice</title>
      <link>https://20andback.co/posts/jason-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://20andback.co/posts/jason-rice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;1&#34;&gt;1.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a child, Jason Rice had a knack for slipping away unnoticed, earning a reputation as an escape artist. He often wandered off, only to be brought back home by police or concerned strangers. His parents made him wear dog tags with their contact information in case he got lost. But after being returned home by the same police officer several times, his parents were warned that if they didn&amp;rsquo;t keep better control of him, he could be taken into state custody. Terrified by the possibility, they frantically searched for a solution and eventually enrolled him in a behavioral program at a local university.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Rae Johnson</title>
      <link>https://20andback.co/posts/morgan-rae-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://20andback.co/posts/morgan-rae-johnson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This account is compiled from multiple interviews given by Morgan. Her website and book are available &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.morganraejohnsonauthor.com&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At five years old, in kindergarten, the military came to Morgan’s classroom. They tested her blood type with a handheld device, pricking her finger in the hallway while other children lined up for recess. The screen read &lt;strong&gt;O negative&lt;/strong&gt;, with a number beneath it: &lt;strong&gt;1.17&lt;/strong&gt;. They asked her if she wanted to meet other kids like her. Before she could fully understand the question, they took her straight to what they called the &lt;em&gt;Elitist Academy&lt;/em&gt;, a government-affiliated school for gifted children somewhere near Fort Lewis, Washington, where ultra soldiers were trained. There were only five children in her class at the time. Kids came from all over the world. Morgan attended intermittently, pulled from school during gymnastics or collected on weekends. She was deeply neglected by her divorced parents. Her twenty-year-old mother was distracted by a boyfriend and rarely noticed when Morgan was gone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Rodrigues</title>
      <link>https://20andback.co/posts/tony-rodrigues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://20andback.co/posts/tony-rodrigues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a summary of Tony’s testimony as he tells it during public appearances and interviews. The full story, told in all its detail, appears in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Ceres-Colony-Cavalier-Account-Abduction/dp/B09PHH7LC7&#34;&gt;Ceres Colony Cavalier&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Project-Starmaker-Cavalier-Collection-Stories/dp/B0C52JNHFP/133-0108678-1383309&#34;&gt;Project Starmaker&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michael Anthony Rodrigues was born in 1972 in Ann Arbor, Michigan. At the time of writing, Tony is 52 years old—yet he carries more than 72 years of memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On April 15th, 1982, after a confrontation at school with a boy who claimed his father was an Illuminati, Tony woke in the middle of the night to find gray aliens standing in his bedroom. They took him from his home and transported him to an underground or off-world facility. There, he was inducted into the &lt;em&gt;20 and back&lt;/em&gt; program, also known as the Career Return program. Through exotic technologies involving cloning and consciousness transfer, Tony lived an additional 20 years of life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
